Hey guys what's up Howard
buenas me chavalería qué pasa howard
Diaz del Rio why are you all
díaz del río porque es que me estáis
thinking so much about the comments but in
pensando tanto los comentarios pero en
the great list in the new liquor group we
el lista gran en el nuevo grupo de licor
have a new group of records I
que tenemos un nuevo grupo de discos me
imagine that everything is already left so much
imagino que ya todo está dejar tanto
but if there is someone who is not yet
pero si hay alguien que todavía no esté
online the description okay we
está en línea la descripción vale
have a new group a server in
tenemos en un nuevo grupo un servidor en
force that covers them tango being full
vigor que los tape tango estando lleno
of god of [ __ ] we are doing
de dios de [__] estamos realizando
naval but I am all these sides that
navales pero estoy todos estos lados que
answer doc and that other video to
le contestan doc y que la otro vídeo al
doc and but why does he want
doc y pero para qué quiere que le haga
me to make another video to doc and on top of
yo otro vídeo al doc y que encima ya de
that I gave him I do and truth and he has
la que le daba hago y verdad y lo ha
left it still goes down in a
dejado todavía va por los suelos de
punctual manner on twitter twitter twitter
manera puntual en el twitter twitter
twitter the [ __ ] my sister what do you
twitter twitter el [__] mi hermana que
take was I put a tweet saying
toman era puse un tweet diciendo que
man that it is the best we reached a thousand
hombre que sea lo mejor llegábamos a mil
challenge and no that he saw us that he was there
reto y no que nos veía que estaba ahí
bursting at the seams well now I would make another
reventa de gana pues ahora hacia otro
video and it took quique I see that he needs
vídeo y tardó quique veo que necesita
the carísima a little more lorea
que la carísima un poquito más lorea
but I am not seeing us an animal he is up to
pero no nos estoy viendo un animal está
things calmer than
hasta las cosas más tranquilita que
before it seems that he already knew
antes se ve que ya sabía
satisfied so  moment let's
satisfecho así que de momento vamos
leave puppy there's a little bit to the side
dejar cachorro hay un poquito de lado
so I decided to record this video today
entonces decidió grabar este vídeo hoy
because I bought that lamp and it's it's
porque me he comprado esa lámpara y es
a beauty it's a [ __ ]
que es es una belleza es una [__]
beautiful lamp lip videos and I
belleza de lámpara vídeos de labios y
decided to record this video today because
decidió grabar este vídeo hoy porque
also another thing that you're asking me
también otra cosa que me estáis pidiendo
a lot both on social networks in the
un montón tanto en redes en los
comments of any video and on
comentarios de cualquier vídeo como en
the album is that I explained that
el disco es que os expliqué que la
last time my friend now test you haven't and
pasada mi colega now test no habéis y
then I say let's make a little video I'll
entonces digo vamos hacer un videíto os
explain it to you and I'm going to locate it and out
lo explico y os voy a localizar and out
airplay okay so you can keep track of it about the
airplay vale para que podáis seguirle la
child supports no that's good they
pista lo del niño apoya no que qué bueno
also put the title that the
ponen también el título que las quita el
channel removes them child [ __ ] in the solo position to
canal niño [__] en el solo puesto para
gain more views but anyway if you want me to
ganar más visitas pero bueno si queréis
talk about the child supports then child supports
que hable el niño apoya pues niño apoya
whitey the channel hasn't even supported them and
a blanquito al canal ni apoyar han
the channel and I just
quitado y el canal y yo justamente hace
a couple of days ago well you know that
un par de días bueno ya sabéis que hace
a week ago things and they threw out a video
una semana cosas y me tiraron un vídeo
for sexual content and be careful because
por contenido sexual y cuidado porque
a man without a shirt appeared
salía un hombre sin camiseta
so I appealed it's brought they rejected my
entonces yo apelé se trae me rechazaron
appeal so he supports it and
la apelación para que la apoya y
he killed me come on incredible fairy that was
er mato vamos increíble hada que tenía
useful for them to remove me  this suit
utilidad para que me quiten este traje
no and now I'm seeing that the
no y ahora yo estoy viendo que el niño
[ __ ] boy apart from being the [ __ ] boy
[__] aparte de que es el niño [__]
uploads a video there are porn actresses in the
sube vídeo hay con actrices porno en la
last thumbnail a bunch of
última miniatura sale un montón de
women in thongs on the way that bothers me it
mujeres en tanga camino que me moleste a
seems like a normal thing but with me
mí me parece una cosa normal pero con yo
that you are throwing a video at me for
que me estás tirando a mí un vídeo por
a guy without a shirt and now this kid
un tío sin camiseta y ahora este niño
puts the girl in a thong in the thumbnail well
pone a la tía en tanga en la miniatura
I said that you touched the balls what
pues yo dije que tocaste los huevos lo
is money no and I did not want to put to I did not
que es la pela no y no quise poner a no
want to put on twitter because you are
quise poner en el twitter porque ya me
going to tell me that over envious and if I am
vais a decir que sobre envidioso y si yo
envious of the [ __ ] boy the
le tengo envidia al niño [__] las
large visits that he has place of
grandes visitas que tiene lugar de
subscribers to get neither time
suscriptores de conseguir tampoco tiempo
but it is a healthy envy I do not have one
pero es una envidia sana no tengo una en
against it much less what does
contra de ni mucho menos lo que sí me
touch my [ __ ] is that so the
toca a la [__] que es que así que las
rules are not the same for everyone and just as they are
normas no son iguales para todos y al
not the same for everyone is
igual que no son iguales para todos es
that youtube does not work me you the same
que youtube no funciona yo tú lo mismo
grabs you and throws you to move me they
te coge y te tira a mover a mí me
put an age restriction on a video
pusieron restricción de edad en un vídeo
that was a [ __ ] top a dad four times
que era un [__] top un papá cuatro veces
that gives me for making a [ __ ] top
que me da por haciendo un [__] top
the most family friley thing that I have done in the
lo más family friley que hecho en la
[ __ ] life so it's a top more
[__] vida así es que es un top más
family subsidiary and with the almost take that
familia filial y con la casi tome que
speaks more they call line or it could be and you
habla más llaman line o podría ser y me
catch me and they take away the monetization of that
coges y me quitan la monetización de ese
video or when I have other videos
vídeo o le cuando tengo otros vídeos
staying in all the dead of all
quedándome en todos los muertos de toda
the people and well monetize doki's milestone and it turns
la gente y bien monetizar hito de doki y
out that we had put in the
nos resulta que había metido en el
chicken boy's twitter finally
twitter del niño pollo a finalmente
rolling term [ __ ] careful what was
enrollando término [__] cuidado lo
put in the title the sleeve for the
puesto en el título la manga para las
visits and in the end I got into the
visitas y al final me metí en el twitter
child's twitter supports and says that it has been thrown down
del niño apoya y pone que ha sido tirado
for identity theft or in other words it's that
por suplantación de identidad o sea es
I had that it doesn't work [ __ ] that it doesn't
que yo tuve que no funciona [__] que no
work my son then nothing like
funciona hijo mío entonces nada como
anything to add to the [ __ ] boy there are
cosa que añadir a lo del niño [__] que
a lot of scavengers these
hay un montón de carroñeros esto sí que
are real scavengers not creating
son carroñeros de verdad no creándose
accounts taking advantage of the fact that they are face of the
cuentas aprovechando que están cara del
[ __ ] boy thrown and he is there creating
niño [__] tirado y está ahí creándose
accounts with the same avatar the same go
cuentas con el mismo avatar el mismo van
in the same name as the real [ __ ] boy it's
en el mismo nombre que el niño [__] de
not that this is very regrettable
verdad no es que esto es muy lamentable
so that he has some subscribers that
para que tiene unos suscriptores que te
follow you like that the rat boy no this same thing
sigan así el niño rata no esto mismo lo
he did
hizo él
one who was sick do you remember that he
uno que estaba malito nos acordáis que
did it with  it pisses me off these people
lo hizo con me toca los [__] éstos
will remember those who have been following for a long
acordaréis los que seguir desde hace
time
tiempo
Reuters play where the [ __ ] Reuters play by
reuter play dónde [__] reuter play por
now templete doctor [ __ ] day on the phone they
now templete doctor [__] día en el móvil
send me the audio in which I
me que me mandan los audio en el que
often see it generates twitter that
muchas veces veo me genera twitter que
people say I forgot that the
la gente dice olvide que el pedazo de
two minute piece of audio sent of three
audio de dos minutos más mandado de tres
minutes in out the fight we sent
minutos en out el pleito nos mandamos
the audios
los audios
of 14 of 20 minutes yurrita call me I
de 14 de 20 minutos yurrita llámame me
[ __ ] on the [ __ ] but it's that I
cago en la [__] pero es que yo encima le
answer him handsome no way you can say
contesto guapeó no vamos se puede decir
that we put ads in the audios and
que le metemos anuncios a los audios y
then what happened to him the
entonces qué es lo que le ha pasado lo
good thing comes in author dragging a
bueno viene en autor arrastrando un
strike from the time it is when I when I had
strike de la época está cuando yo cuando
it so bad with the channel
lo tuve pasado tan chungo con el canal
what I thought was going to lose it that
lo que me creía que lo iba a perder que
Dallas started right and left to
dallas se puso a diestro y siniestro a
throw away all the videos when those from
tirar a todos los vídeos cuando los de
Dallas win Michu is expelled
dallas win michu se expulsa tira de
throws away all the videos they found why Dallas does that that I know that from a good source Dallas sits there with his sticky hair he sits in  the pib computer and
pringoso se siente en el ordenador pib y
starts looking for everything about him,
se pone a buscar todo lo que haya de él
everything, everything they add and they start
todo todito lo que añaden y lo empiezan
reporting him, in fact, back then
a denunciar de hecho por aquel entonces
at that time, well, not with the
en ese momento bueno no con los del
farfan people, with the fake football thing, balls
farfán con lo del fútbol falsas huevos
of [ __ ] that he created, I said a [ __ ]
de [__] que ha creado dije una [__]
garbage game, that's it, you say, your
basura del juego ya está dice tú tu
best friend didn't throw down a page on the
mejor amigo no tiró una página en la
meristation website, it could be good,
página web meristation puede ser bueno
don't correct me, his nickname for the
no me vayas a corregir su apodo de la
light page, a page and he threw it down, not a
página de luz una página y la tiró no un
block that said, fine, that puts
bloque que ponía fino que pone a caldo
the game in hot water, now he says that there was [ __ ] back
el juego ahora dice que hubo una [__]
in the day, I threw that away, well, one,
en su día tiro eso pues a uno
a strike fighter, I got two, no,
un strike fighter a mi me cayeron dos no
what happens is that they solved
que lo que pasa que a mí me solucionaron
the problems for me, as you well know,
los problemas como ya bien sabéis de
[ __ ] great, I continue on my way, let's
[__] madre sigo a mi rollo
see if I wash my hands, by the way, the
a ver si me lavo las manos por cierto la
little hand and in one of the extras
manita un poquito y en uno de los extras
that they put on him, well, they rejected the
que le pusieron pues le rechazaron la
appeal, they didn't consider it valid,
apelación no se lo dieron por válidas
which seems strange to me because
cosa que me parece una extraña porque
you know that in out airplay he's
ustedes saben que en out airplay es
super, he's a super kid, line or super, from
súper es un chaval súper line o súper de
time to time he makes a pedophile of the
vez en cuando le haga pedófilo al agente
carcinogenic agent  and I hope it's not even to
cancerígeno y espero es que tampoco para
throw a video and he uploaded the same video
tirar un vídeo y le subió el mismo vídeo
that they had rejected him to do they
el cual le habían rechazado hacer le
put an extra and a mess of [ __ ] thing and he
meten un extra y lío de [__] cosa y
summarizes the video for his game because he
resume el vídeo por su juego porque
wants that video chain and nothing
quiere que ese vídeo chain y nada no
nothing happens he has it
pasa nada
until January it expires
tiene le trae hasta enero le caduca
now in January that strike is
ahora en enero ese strike
made to look at last month a video
se le hace mirar el mes pasado un vídeo
by lado cabrera that in fact had it
de lado cabrera que de hecho lo tuvo en
trending in a good trending position it
tendencia en un buen puesto de tendencia
has in Argentina and in Uruguay what
tiene en argentina y en uruguay que es
happens with so much cabrera that is
lo que pasa con tanto cabrera que es
dallas and everything is that the channel of those of the
dallas y todo es que el canal de los del
play one part destroys for dallas another
play una parte destruya por dallas otra
part for me to cabrera and he gets
parte por por yo a cabrera no y le cae
a video from the year of the pear or in other words from
un vídeo del año de la pera o sea de
two years ago at least not incredible
hace dos años por lo menos no increíble
total second strike and they also
total segundo strike y también se lo
reject the appeal all this of
rechazan la apelación todo esto de
rejected the appeal is to accept the
rechazada la apelación es aceptar la
note for me for example they cleaned it
nota para mí por ejemplo me lo limpiaron
all this is very relative not many people
todo esto es muy relativo no mucha gente
will say [ __ ] but it is that
dirá ostias pero es que
and of course if later you take your apple as the
y claro si luego coge tu apple as el
video appeals the extra of how high and
vídeo apela el extra de que tan puesto y
youtube watch video and sees a guy who
youtube ver vídeo y ve a un tío que se
is  [ __ ] is everywhere look guys
está [__] hay en todo mira chavales a
they've given me a strike on videos that I
mí me han puesto strike en vídeos que me
[ __ ] what I [ __ ] but from the hotel to
cago lo que me cago pero del hotel a de
[ __ ] on people's dead is worth
cagarme en los muertos de la gente vale
your help I'm going to peel it for the
vuestra ayuda ya lo voy a pelar por la
money and take it off the strike although the
pela y me la quita del strike aunque lo
same thing has been taken videos that had
mismo ha cogido vídeos que no tenían
nothing at least from my criteria that usually happens
nada por lo menos desde mi criterio que
rarely and the appeals
eso suele pasar pocas veces y los apelar
have rejected my appeal well for
me han rechazado la apelación bueno por
example this video is not an extra in
ejemplo este vídeo no es un extra en lo
the monetization that I have told you no the
de la monetización que os he dicho no el
icon has come this balls what
icono ha venido este de los huevos lo
is a family friendly video and it is
que es un vídeo family friendly y se
supposed that I have manually reviewed
supone que he revisado manualmente
ninths monetize and the thing is that you have to
novenos monetizan y es que tenéis que
see the video I tell you it is worthy of
ver vídeo ya os digo es que digno de
Disney Channel that I am editing I just
disney channel que estoy editando me
remembered another thing [ __ ] very
acabo de acordar otra cosa [__] muy
important that also admitted me a strike
importante que también me admitió strike
on a video I have appealed it they have taken away
en un vídeo lo he apelado me han quitado
the premiere they have reviewed it they have seen
el estreno se lo han revisado han visto
the video they had nothing they have returned it to me
el vídeo no tenían nada me lo han
mankita brings them and then they
devuelto mankita les trae y luego me han
put me on strike again on that video
vuelto a meter un strike en ese vídeo
how the hell is that going to be possible if they have already
eso como [__] va a ser posible si ya lo
reviewed it and removed it like  it's
han revisado y me lo quitaron como
possible that they'll
es posible que le vuelvan a meter un
strike him again and now it's okay, don't accept it,
strike y ahora está bien no me lo acepte
really, YouTube, it doesn't make sense,
de verdad youtube que no tiene lógica
your system works less than
vuestro sistema funciona menos que la
Arevalo's dick and I think that
[__] de arévalo y que yo creo que
really there's no one there to review
realmente ahí no hay nadie que revise
the videos and dick no, it all depends on the one
los vídeos y [__] no que todo depende
who sits there that day in
del del que se siente ese día allí en
the YouTube offices and says, "I contributed
las oficinas de youtube y diga me aportó
to the appeals, pa pa pa pa pa pa I
a las apelaciones pa pa pa pa pa pa pa
accept them from each of the buoys, he rejects
las acepto de cada de las boyas rechaza
all potatoes and that's how it goes, that's how it goes, YouTube
toda patata y así va así va de youtube
doesn't work, the bus doesn't work, the
ni funciona ni funciona el bondi
workers don't work, and it doesn't make any
funcionan los trabajadores ni tiene
sense, nothing is a it's like
punto sentido nada es un es es como como
random, not like everything when here at
al azar no como que todo cuando aquí a
the slot machines and what I advised him
las tragaperras y yo lo que le aconseje
was to put all the
quisiera era que pusiera todos los
videos in private and wait until
vídeos en privado y que se esperase a
January, damn son of a [ __ ] wait until January,
enero [__] hijo de [__] espérate a enero
although seriously it waits for you and at
aunque seriamente te espera y por lo
least they take one away, he's with an
menos que te quiten uno está con un
extra and nothing else, he can't smell them like I
extra y nada más no te las huele como
did, I don't know how to remember that I was with
hice yo no sé recordar que yo estuve con
the entire channel closed, the private channel
todo el canal cerrato del canal privado
through they sorted out the problems and that's it,
a través ordenaron los problemas y ya
I prefer to save my ass,
está es que yo prefiero salvar mi culo
not save  because because the [ __ ] is it that the
no salvar porque porque [__] es que el
channel wants it or not and it's not about the
canal quiera que no y ya no es por el
money anymore
dinero
well it continues too no me, for example, I get
bueno sigue también no yo yo por ejemplo
used to
se acostumbra oria
counting on this
a contar en mi casa con este con este
extra income at home it's not money that
sobresueldo no es un dinero con el cual
I'm used to in your day that
estoy acostumbrado en tu ser día que
from youtube you may miss but
desde youtube puede echar en falta pero
not about the money no because looking on
ya no sobre el dinero no ya que mira en
youtube well you meet people you make
youtube pues conoces gente coges
friends with people I make a lot both
amistades con gente yo cogió mucha tanto
enemies and friends no but it
enemistades como amistades no pero sí
's true the power a lot buddy
que es verdad el poder mucho compadre
with a lot of people with whom I talk to
con mucha gente con las cuales hablo a
daily I have gone out entered fear of traveling
diario he salido entrado miedo de viaje
a lot of things no him and I for example
montón de cosas no él y yo por ejemplo
have a complicity we talk about
tenemos una complicidad que hablamos a
daily as I already told you the hours that you
diario como ya os digo las horas que le
dedicate to the computer many hours that it
dedicas al ordenador muchas horas que te
takes away from you the best of doing something
las quita lo mejor de estar haciendo
else is having a beer with your
otra cosa está tomando una cerveza con
friends is with your girlfriend on one
los colegas de está con tu novia en un
side of her on the couch touching your
lado de esta en el sofá tocándote un
balls are hours that you take away from your
huevo son horas que tú te quitas de tu
life and but now it is but now I
vida y pero ahora es pero ahora ya os
tell you that you believe that no but
digo yo que os creéis que no pero
we dedicate some incredible hours here
nosotros dedicamos aquí unas horas
that if you want to achieve something you
increíbles que si tú quieres llegar algo
have to put dedication here no  there
tienes que poner aquí dedicación no no
are people who take it upon themselves to believe the channel and
hay gente que coge se cree el canal y
do what everyone else does in their
hace lo que hace todo el mundo en sus
videos and talk a controversy about three or
vídeos y habla una polémica de tres o
four secret things and with that yes no no
cuatro cosas secret y con eso sí no no
no you have to be on your feet all day
no las tienes que estar todo el día de
and it's a shame it's a shame that your
y es una pena es una pena que te cierre
channel is closed and all that goes to the trash
un canal y todo eso se vaya a la basura
all that is as if you take studying for
todo eso es como si tú coges estudia por
example it has nothing to do with it of course
ejemplo no tiene na que ver por supuesto
not before you tell me anything I already
no antes de que me digáis nada ya lo
said it no but imagine that you
digo yo no pero imagínate que tú te
spend two or three years studying a
pegas dos o tres años estudiando una
degree and every afternoon you are working hard on this
carrera y todas las tardes hincando los
thing and a month before you take it and you and you you
codos del rollo y un mes antes coges y t
delete it or you get expelled you haven't
y t y t borras o te expulsan no
wasted time of your life time when you
has perdido tiempo de tu vida tiempo
could have invested it in something else
pudiendo haberlo invertido en otra cosa
then he took it the day one arrived that
entonces cogió llegó el día uno que ya
this two
se le terminaba el castigo este de dos
week punishment on his videos was about to end and instead of
semanas en sus vídeos y en vez de
waiting he uploaded a video uploads a
esperarse se subió un vídeo sube un
video saying I'm back I didn't get to
vídeo diciendo he vuelto yo no llegué a
see this video but he took the video and they
ver este vídeo pero cogió el vídeo y se
threw it away too third strike channel
lo tiraron también tercer strike canal
closed now what is happening well be it if he
cerrado ahora qué es lo que pasan pues
complains he is complaining
que sea si reclama está reclamando
you are fighting  what I
estáis luchando lo
think are a little more is that I don't
yo creo que son un poco más
know why there are people who also
es que no sé por qué hay gente también
want to close the channel and have
quieren cerrar el canal y le han
answered the email
contestado a email
is that I have not done that the salt as I am
es que no he hecho esa la sal como estoy
saying
diciendo
if the fig falls to you info I had recovered his
si te cae la breva info tuve recuperó su
channel after everything that Jairo
canal después de todo lo que tenía jairo
Bleu had also had the three strikes they
bleu también tuvo los tres strikes les
closed the channel and he recovered it I do not think there will
cerraron el canal y lo recuperó no yo
be luck hopefully and he will
creo que habrá suerte ojalá y se lo se
return it to him no of course because I know
lo devuelva no por supuesto porque sé
that they invest many hours with him and with
que invierten muchas horas con él y con
a piece of [ __ ] he is a [ __ ] [ __ ]
un pedazo de cabrón es un cabronazo de
that pisses you off but that he is
la [__] de la que te caga pero que es
very funny and I am I really
muy divertido y estoy yo de verdad lo
say it I am with the audios you
digo yo estoy con los audios ustedes
imagined one of my conversations and
imaginaron uno las conversaciones mía y
the audios how can it be good to
de los audios como puede ser bueno a
all this the 33 that he has is cut but
todo esto se corta los 33 que tiene pero
to all this through lies like
a todo esto por medio de mentiras como
another three or four harder per week
otros tres o cuatro más duro por semana
that if he was appealing to him and if they
que si le le fue apelando y si se la
accepted it no but it is that she is as if she
aceptaron no pero es que ella es como si
were someone behind reporting
estuviera a alguien detrás denunciando
the videos because in addition unesco the
los vídeos porque además unesco sean los
videos are super active many times
vídeos súper activos muchas veces uno
only 11 of the 'stress was because of the
solo 11 de los 'stress fue por la
label that says  that they were
etiqueta que dice que eran etiquetas
misleading labels when they were labels that
engañosas cuando eran etiquetas que
actually corresponded to the video
realmente corresponden con el vídeo
well there yesterday taller jairo blog
bueno allí ayer taller jairo blog
aero they threw a video at him twice
aero le tiraron dos veces un vídeo una
once they told him that the label had
vez le dijeron que tenía la etiqueta
too much label and another time about too little
demasiada etiqueta y otra vez de la poca
label I think it's that u2 you are
etiqueta yo creo que es que u2 tú estás
crazy and the moment
como una [__] [__] y en el momento que
another platform comes out you want to
salga otra plataforma hacerte la
compete with it I think you're going to be on fire
competencia yo creo que lo llevas humo
on youtube although now a lot of people are
en youtube aunque ahora mucha gente está
leaving I can tell you all the
se está yendo te doy cuenta ya todos los
usual youtubers that are seen on
youtubers habituales que se le ve en
our screens not many of them are
nuestras pantallas ya no muchos de ellos
no longer there at the forefront like a
ya no están ahí al pie del cañón como
guy and nothing basically we are
chabán y nada básicamente que estamos
discouraged okay I wanted to say it that I
desanimados vale quería decirlo eso
wanted to convey how
quería transmitir lo que estamos
discouraged we are that he doesn't give a damn
desanimados que se la mete en un huevo
now that he doesn't do that he's not going to come back
ahora que no haga que no va a volver
tower I told them that he's going to come back
torre les he dicho que va a volver
because I don't know what it is about
porque yo no sé qué es lo que tiene
youtube that is not what youtube has
youtube de no ser lo que tiene youtube
but we can't live without it not
pero tampoco podemos vivir sin él no
even if you demonetize the videos that
aunque te des monetice en los vídeos que
even if it pisses you off that if this that if that
aunque te empute en que si esto que si
but it has one thing that I for
lo otro pero tiene una cosa que a mí por
example that I love I love it
ejemplo que me encantan a mí me encanta
is here he is commenting  with you he
está aquí está comentando con ustedes me
recorded me in my life and all my little things
grabó en mi vida y todos mis cositas
but right now we are discouraged he
pero ahora mismo estamos desanimados
is with his dick very touched also also
está con la [__] muy tocada también
all the videos were
también también todos los vídeos se lo
put in yellow also no me
ponían en amarillo también no yo eso por
unfortunately I am not living it that much there is not a
desgracia no lo estoy viviendo tanto no
little video I have in yellow
hay un poco vídeo tengo en amarillo
yes it is true that maybe the
el sí que es verdad que a lo mejor los
youtube videos the videos that are
vídeos de youtube los videos que son de
two minutes long with images that he does not
dos minutos en con imágenes que él no se
record but those videos take them
graba pero esos vídeos les les llevan
many more hours than maybe me that as I
muchas más horas que a lo mejor yo que
put the webcam I turn it off and
como pongo la webcam la quito y
lately that I am in a lazy mood let's
últimamente que estoy en plan vago vamos
see am I am complicating life a lot
a ver amestoy complicando mucho la vida
but those videos that make aute
pero eso los vídeos que hacen aute
because he has to look for an image for
porque tiene que buscar una imagen para
a word you see that giving another image for
una palabra ven que dar otra imagen para
another words to the other image will make an
otra palabras a la otra imagen hará un
effect brought him closer in which it sticks
efecto le acercó en el que se pega
many times four or five hours being
muchas veces cuatro o cinco horas siendo
a two minute video so that now
un vídeo de dos minutos para que ahora
thing you upload it and have it from monet and if
cosa tú lo subes y tenerlo de monet y si
I the truth if it does not only return well it
yo la verdad si no sólo devuelve pues
had an out it was now you go to your
tuvo un out era ahora te vas a tu canal
secondary channel they are called out the without filter
secundario se llaman out el sin filtro
what you want well not what you want
lo que queréis bueno no lo que queréis
not all of you who are watching this
no todos los que estáis viendo este
video  you're going to go and subscribe to
vídeo os vais a ir y os vais a suscribir
the [ __ ] channel and vice, come on,
el [__] canal y vice
one thing nostra post, go the
vamos una cosa nostra post os vayáis el
secondary channel called authers
canal secundario que se llaman authers
without filter uploaded a video today that
sin filtro ha subido un vídeo hoy que
says so I know this guy is
dice que entonces sé que este tío está
crazy he says it's obvious
como una [__] [__] dice es evidente
videos like a testament no no with this
vídeos como un testamento no no con esta
explanation but I'm going go to that
explicación pero ya me voy vaya a ese
video and you're going to put out airplay
vídeo y le vais a poner out airplay
but think naut airplay you're going to upload
pero piense naut airplay vas a subir
videos or javi oliveira is cool ar
vídeos o javi oliveira está chucha ar
doc and that's what I'm going to put the
doc y eso es lo que le voy a poner los
comments a little long but I know
comentarios un poquito largo pero yo sé
that you guys go be capable and nothing
que ustedes vaya sean capaces y nada
guys one more thing lastly I'm going
chavales otra cosita más por último voy
to record a video with the toca huevo
a grabar un vídeo con el toca huevo
[Music]
[Música]
what do you prefer it's not the typical video this one
qué prefieres no es el típico vídeo está
asks you a compromising question
que te hace una pregunta comprometida
what do you prefer these the others no you
qué prefieres estos los otros no ya
know what I'm very smart about you guys
sabes de lo que soy muy listo ustedes
so if you want to participate in giving us
entonces si queréis participar en darnos
the question we're going to record it tomorrow you
la pregunta lo vamos a grabar mañana
have to be at full capacity tonight until
tenéis que estar esta noche a tope hasta
tomorrow when we record it and on the
que hasta mañana que lo grabamos y en el
hashtag
hashtag
javi toca on the hashtag javi toca
javi toca en el hashtag javi toca
habitat have you seen  As I say, hashtag
hábitat habéis visto como digo hashtag
in the hashtag javito, here we are going to read the
en el hashtag javito acá vamos a leer la
question that is put there, be original
pregunta que nos ponga ahí se originales
sons of [ __ ] and don't put milestones of
hijos de [__] y no me ponga hitos del
Giau Cabrera and that damn Dallas, okay,
giau cabrera y del puñetero dallas vale
see you gentlemen, may the kings bring you lots of
nos vemos señores que os traiga muchas
things and may they [ __ ] you.
cositas los reyes y que os den por culo